The year is 20XX. You glance out at a city overcast and gray; this metropolis is a utopia, as long as you stay in line. But your very existence, a lone piece of graffiti in a world otherwise devoid of artistic expression, threatens the sanctity of the established system. The Bureau of Artistic Development (BAD), a “regulatory” organization which has its eyes on most of the city, has sent propaganda agents to erase you. Thus, with nothing but a handy paint ball gun and as much paint as you can fit on your person, you set out to create a world that will accept your existence...

a true​ paradise.